freebetting.net 2008-12-17

# Privacy Policy - Free Betting guide

**Privacy Policy**

[FreeBetting.net](http://www.freebetting.net/) knows that your privacy is important to you and recognizes your right to maintain your privacy on the web and beyond. 

[FreeBetting.net](http://www.freebetting.net/) guarantees that no private information about you will be shared with any third party unless [FreeBetting.net](http://www.freebetting.net/) has reason to believe you are causing interference or injury to [FreeBetting.net](http://www.freebetting.net/), its affiliates or agents, in which case information will only be used for legal purposes. 

[FreeBetting.net](http://www.freebetting.net/) may share aggregate demographic information about users to advertisers and others for the purposes of customizing ads for the site. For example, FreeBetting.net might say that x% of users live in the Europe, but no personal information will be revealed. 

[FreeBetting.net](http://www.freebetting.net/) does not and will not link personal information about you to your IP address (your IP address is the number that's automatically assigned to your computer when you're on the net) unless [FreeBetting.net](http://www.freebetting.net/) feels it's necessary to enforce its policies, protect its interests, and protect the interest of our customers. 

[FreeBetting.net](http://www.freebetting.net/) contains links to other sites. [FreeBetting.net](http://www.freebetting.net/) is not responsible for the privacy, the practices, or the content of such web sites. 

By using the [FreeBetting.net](http://www.freebetting.net/) web site you are consenting to the privacy policy as described and also consent to understanding the Disclaimer information. [FreeBetting.net](http://www.freebetting.net/) reserves the right to change its privacy policy at any time and in the event that a change has occurred changes it will be posted on this page. 

Forms you fill out to interact with our company may request that you give us sensitive information such as your e-mail address, mailing address, or telephone number. [FreeBetting.net](http://www.freebetting.net/) treats these communications with high respect and will not use data gathered from the Web site in any way other than to understand customer needs and inquiries, similar to an ordinary phone call or a fax transmission. 

[FreeBetting.net](http://www.freebetting.net/) takes no responsibility for interception of data by third parties.
